CONGRESS SHOULD BAN FRACKING ON FED LANDS A new Environment <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> report highlights fracking s dirty track record. The analysis of the oil and gas industry in <LOCATION>Pennsylvania</LOCATION> shows that all types of gas fracking companies are prone to infractions of environmental and public health protections. Over a nearly four-year period, the top 20 violators of regulations included Fortune 500 companies, mom-and-pop operators and even companies like Chevron, which tout their green records. Taken altogether, the worst offenders averaged a violation every single day that posed real risks to human health, air quality or drinking water. This is just the latest study showing that fracking is a failure for our environment and health. That s why we re calling on <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> s congressional delegation to support a ban on fracking on federal public lands. <PERSON>Heather Leibowitz</PERSON>  <LOCATION>New York City</LOCATION> The writer is director of Environment New York. I just read <PERSON>Mike MacAdam</PERSON> s <DATE>March 11</DATE> A Seat in the Bleachers column [ Losses keep piling up for <ORGANIZATION>Union College</ORGANIZATION> women s hockey ], and though I don t always agree with him, he raised some valid points about <ORGANIZATION>Union</ORGANIZATION> s women s ice hockey team. First, I love watching ice hockey and used to love coaching and playing until my legs retired. Second, women s ice hockey isn t as fast or physical as men s hockey. But in part because it isn t as fast or as physical, it can showcase more skills and playmaking. For me, both men s and women s hockey games are exciting and interesting to watch. The same cannot be said for the <ORGANIZATION>Union College</ORGANIZATION> men s and women s ice hockey teams. Although the skill levels of <ORGANIZATION>Union</ORGANIZATION> s women s and men s teams have improved dramatically over the early years of Division 1, I don t believe the women s coaching has. Furthermore, I am concerned that this situation may be allowed to continue because of a sexual bias that men should enjoy winning games while women should just enjoy playing them. I doubt that a men s hockey coach at <ORGANIZATION>Union</ORGANIZATION> would be allowed to continue with such little progress after eight years. I suspect that what little progress has been shown by the women s team is due more to a few short-lived excellent assistant coaches than the head coach. <PERSON>Stephen Anderson</PERSON> Charlton It is particularly distressing to hear that the governor and the Legislature cannot agree to reauthorize renewal of design-build legislation for <ORGANIZATION>New York. The Design-Build Institute of America</ORGANIZATION> has released research findings indicating that for the first time, more than half of projects in the <LOCATION>United States</LOCATION> above $10 million are being completed through design-build project delivery. It is indeed a great tool to repair our transportation and infrastructure projects in a fast, efficient manner. However, the <PERSON>Cuomo</PERSON> administration has tied design-build to mandatory project labor agreements (PLAs). PLAs mandate union-only projects and are unrelated to extending design-build legislation. PLAs are simply politically motivated to serve special interest groups. Design-build legislation needs to be an available tool to public agencies without any restrictions so that both union and merit-shop contractors can compete in the free marketplace using innovative and unique approaches to solve problems without a government mandate of what type of labor needs to be employed on the project. If a union contractor can give a better value than a merit-shop contractor, the taxpayer wins. <LOCATION>America</LOCATION> is built on the free enterprise system that works amazingly well. However, it is truly the taxpayers of <LOCATION>New York</LOCATION> state who once again lose. Fixing our infrastructure doesn t buy votes and it is a problem that won t be going away. Unrestricted design-build legislation could be part of the solution. <PERSON>Dave Rakvica Mayfield</PERSON> The writer is a vice president of construction for <ORGANIZATION>Schultz Construction. The Gazette</ORGANIZATION> welcomes reader opinions on public issues. For information on how to send a letter to the editor, see the bottom of this page. For more letters, visit our website: www.dailygazette.com . Shorter letters are encouraged and will be given preference as to timeliness and space. There is no strict word limit, though letters of about 200-300 words are preferred. Excessively long letters will be published online only. All letters are subject to editing for length, style and <ORGANIZATION>fairness. Writers</ORGANIZATION> are limited to one letter every 30 days. Please include your signature, address and daytime phone number for verification.