SIENA WOMEN-S SOCCER TEAM EXTENDS WIN STREAK TO 10 GAMES JERSEY CITY, <LOCATION>N.J.</LOCATION> Soph omore <PERSON>Caitlin Cahalan,</PERSON> a graduate of Shaker High School, and <PERSON>Lindsay Tegas</PERSON> scored in the first 16 minutes <DATE>Sunday</DATE> to lead the <LOCATION>Siena</LOCATION> women s soccer team to its 10th straight win, a 2-1 decision over <PERSON>Saint Peter</PERSON> s in the <LOCATION>Metro Atlantic</LOCATION> Athletic Conference. The Saints, the only undefeated and untied women s division I program in the nation, also improved their road record to 8-0. It was nice to get another win on the road, said <LOCATION>Siena</LOCATION> coach <PERSON>Steve Karbowski.</PERSON> You have to play under different conditions, and it prepares you more for the rest of the conference, and hopefully, the postseason. <PERSON>Cahalan</PERSON> scored off a long pass from <PERSON>Jenna Placke</PERSON> at 6:41, and Tegas scored her third goal of the year on a headball at 16:33, knocking in a cross by <PERSON>Ashleigh Barone</PERSON> of Shenendehowa. <PERSON>Elizabeth Barna</PERSON> stopped three shots for the Saints, who host perennial MAAC power <LOCATION>Loyola</LOCATION> on Friday. <LOCATION>Siena</LOCATION> 2 0 2 <PERSON>Saint Peter</PERSON> s 1 0 1 <LOCATION>Siena</LOCATION> scoring: <PERSON>Caitlin Cahalan</PERSON> 1-0, Lindsay Tegas 1-0, <PERSON>Jenna Placke 0-1, Ashleigh Barone 0-1. Saint Peter</PERSON> s scoring: <PERSON>Emily Fenice</PERSON> 1-0. Goalies: Siena, Elizabeth Barna, 3 saves. Saint <PERSON>Peter s, Erin Ronan,</PERSON> 7 saves. WEST HARTFORD, Conn. <PERSON>Breanna Maggio</PERSON> made all three of her saves in the first half to record her sixth career shutout as the <LOCATION>Great Danes</LOCATION> picked up their first point of the year in the <LOCATION>America</LOCATION> East Conference. <PERSON>Lauren Brodeur</PERSON> earned her fifth shutout of the year for the Hawks (4-6-3, 1-0-2 AE). The <PERSON>Danes</PERSON> are 0-1-1 in the league and 5-6-1 overall. The Great <PERSON>Danes</PERSON> had their best scoring opportunity near the end of regulation, when <PERSON>Chrissy Klepper</PERSON> got the ball to <PERSON>Aubrey VanGorder</PERSON> near the post. But <PERSON>VanGorder</PERSON> s shot sailed just wide. UAlbany 0 0 0 0 0 <LOCATION>Hartford</LOCATION> 0 0 0 0 0 Goalies: UAlbany, Breanne Maggio, 3 saves. Hartford, Lauren Brodeur, 5 saves. <LOCATION>COBLESKILL</LOCATION> Sophomore <PERSON>Megan Frailey</PERSON> scored three goals and picked up an assist to lead <LOCATION>Penn State Harrisburg</LOCATION> to a <ORGANIZATION>North Eastern Athletic Conference</ORGANIZATION> victory. The loss dropped the <ORGANIZATION>Fighting Tigers</ORGANIZATION> to 3-3 in the league and 5-6-1 overall. <LOCATION>Penn State Harrisburg</LOCATION> 3 4 7 SUNY-Cobleskill 0 0 0 <ORGANIZATION>Penn State Harrisburg</ORGANIZATION> scoring: <PERSON>Megan Frailey</PERSON> 3-1, <PERSON>Jessie Manion</PERSON> 2-1, <PERSON>Amanda Shaffer</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Lindsey McNeal</PERSON> 1-1, <PERSON>Adrienne Stine</PERSON> 0-1, <PERSON>Erin Murphy</PERSON> 0-1. Goalies: <ORGANIZATION>Penn State</ORGANIZATION> Harrisburg, Brittany Adams, 12 saves. SUNY-Cobleskill, <PERSON>Katelyn</PERSON> Benjamin, 12 saves; Misty Golden, 10 saves. <LOCATION>COBLESKILL</LOCATION> Sophomore <PERSON>Dillion Sobilo</PERSON> scored a pair of first-half goals as <ORGANIZATION>Penn State Harrisburg</ORGANIZATION> ran its NEAC record to 4-1. <PERSON>Sophomore Diego Lopez</PERSON> scored off a feed from freshman <PERSON>Souleymane Kone</PERSON> for the <ORGANIZATION>Fighting Tigers (2-7-1, 0-4-1 NEAC). Penn State Harrisburg 2</ORGANIZATION>  <DATE>1 3 SUNY-Cobleskill 0 1 1</DATE>  <ORGANIZATION>Penn State Harrisburg scoring: Dillion Sobilo</ORGANIZATION> 2-0, <PERSON>Daniel Francis</PERSON> 1-0, SUNY-Cobleskill scoring: <PERSON>Diego Lopez</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Souleymane Kone</PERSON> 0-1. Goalies: <ORGANIZATION>Penn State</ORGANIZATION> Harrisburg, <PERSON>Josh</PERSON> Wolff, 2 saves. SUNY-Cobleskill, <PERSON>Patrick Cobanem</PERSON> 1 save; Mack Curran, 7 saves. <LOCATION>NEW YORK</LOCATION>  <PERSON>Steve Chikwem</PERSON> scored two goals as <ORGANIZATION>Albany College of Pharmacy</ORGANIZATION> picked up its seventh win in nine starts. <ORGANIZATION>ACP</ORGANIZATION> 0 4 4 <PERSON>Sarah Lawrence</PERSON> 0 1 1 <ORGANIZATION>ACP</ORGANIZATION> scoring: <PERSON>Steve Chikwem</PERSON> 2-0, <PERSON>Kyle Caradori</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Chris Wasacz 1-0, Zachary Hecox</PERSON> 0-2, <PERSON>Andrew Levy 0-1. Sarah Lawrence scoring: Rodrigo Cuenca</PERSON> 1-0. Goalies: ACP, Adam Hoye-Simek, 6 saves. <PERSON>Sarah Lawrence, Codey</PERSON> Foster, 5 saves. PROVIDENCE, R.I. <PERSON>Christina Patrick</PERSON> scored the game-winning goal off an assist from <PERSON>Daphne Voormolen</PERSON> in the 47th minute as the 17th-ranked Great <PERSON>Danes</PERSON> rallied to defeat the <ORGANIZATION>Friars</ORGANIZATION> in a non-conference game. <PERSON>Voormolen</PERSON> and <PERSON>Corrine McConville</PERSON> also scored the the Great Danes (10-2), who fell behind, 2-1, early in the second half. <DATE>UAlbany 1 2 3 Providence 1 1 2</DATE> UAlbany scoring: <PERSON>Daphne Voormolen</PERSON> 1-1, <PERSON>Christina Patrick 1-1, Corrine McConville</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Ashlyn Bach 0-1, Alysia Hough</PERSON> 0-1. <LOCATION>Providence</LOCATION> scoring: <PERSON>Ashlyn Hudson 1-1, Kelly Grogan</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Jaime Lipski 0-1. Hillary Anderson</PERSON> 0-1. Goalies: UAlbany, <PERSON>Christine</PERSON> Hoffman, 1 save; <PERSON>Kristi</PERSON> Troch, 0 saves. Providence, <PERSON>Kathi</PERSON> Weldman, 4 saves. BURLINGTON, Vt. <PERSON>Taylor Silvestro</PERSON> scored the only goal of the game early in the second half as the Catamounts dropped the Saints to 1-9. <LOCATION>Siena</LOCATION> 0 0 0 <LOCATION>Vermont</LOCATION> 0 1 1 <LOCATION>Vermont</LOCATION> scoring: <PERSON>Taylor Silvestro 1-0, Jenna Horowski</PERSON> 0-1. Goalies: Siena, Beth Meyers, 10 saves. Vermont, <PERSON>Brooke Crane,</PERSON> 5 saves. <LOCATION>UTICA</LOCATION>  <PERSON>Christine Kemp</PERSON> set up two goals as the Thoroughbreds improved their record to 8-1 with a non-conference victory. <PERSON>Kelly Blackhurst</PERSON> scored her ninth goal of the season, and <PERSON>Brittany O Brien</PERSON> and <PERSON>Claire Superak</PERSON> had the other goals for Skidmore. Skidmore 3 0 3 <LOCATION>Utica</LOCATION> 0 0 0 Skidmore scoring: <PERSON>Brittany O Brien</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Claire Superak 1-0, Kelly Blackhurst</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Christine Kemp</PERSON> 0-2. Goalies: Skidmore, Liz Catinella, 2 saves; Margaux Hoagland, 0 saves. Utica, Monica Storms, 14 saves. LAWRENCEVILLE, <LOCATION>N.J.</LOCATION>  <PERSON>Eliz abeth Ives</PERSON> had seven of <LOCATION>Siena</LOCATION> s aces, and <PERSON>Taylor Akana</PERSON> led all players with 20 kills as <LOCATION>Siena</LOCATION> defeated Rider, 17-25, 25-17, 25-19, 27-25, to even its <ORGANIZATION>Metro Atlantic Athletic Conference</ORGANIZATION> record at 3-3. <LOCATION>Leslia Akeo</LOCATION> had 17 digs for <LOCATION>Siena</LOCATION> (4-11 overall), and <PERSON>Brianne Bobo</PERSON> (13) and <PERSON>Sarah Horvath</PERSON> (11) also recorded double-digit digs. <PERSON>Katelyn Thompson</PERSON> led the Broncs (1-14, 0-6) with 17 kills.