DESALVO, FONCETTE LIFT GREAT DANES, 1-0 <LOCATION>ALBANY</LOCATION> &#151; In a battle of cross-county rivals, University at Alb any s men s soccer team edged Siena, 1-0, when <PERSON>Anthony DeSalvo</PERSON> scored in the 79th minute off an assist from <PERSON>Jeff Pierre</PERSON>  <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> at <ORGANIZATION>Varsity Field. Adrian Foncette</ORGANIZATION> made three saves for the Great Danes. <PERSON>Phil Chabot</PERSON> stopped two shots for Siena. The Danes, who have shut out the Saints in three straight meetings, improve to 3-2, while <LOCATION>Siena</LOCATION> drops to 1-3. <LOCATION>Siena</LOCATION> 0 0 0 <LOCATION>Albany</LOCATION> 0 1 1 <LOCATION>Albany</LOCATION> scoring: <PERSON>Anthony DeSalvo</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Jeff Pierre 0-1.</PERSON> Goalies: Siena, <PERSON>Phil</PERSON> Chabot, 2 saves; Albany, Adrian Foncette, 3 saves. <LOCATION>UTICA</LOCATION>  <PERSON>Roberto Squeglia</PERSON> knocked in a penalty kick 6:30 into overtime to carry the Pioneers over the Thoroughbreds. <ORGANIZATION>DJ Ilebani</ORGANIZATION> also scored for 5-1 Utica. <PERSON>Matt Kelsey</PERSON> scored for 3-2-1 Skidmore. Skidmore 0 1 0 1 <LOCATION>Utica</LOCATION> 0 1 1 2 Skidmore scoring: <PERSON>Matt Kelsey 1-0, Greg Lloyd 0-1.</PERSON>  <LOCATION>Utica</LOCATION> scoring: DJ Ilebani 1-0, <PERSON>Roberto Squeglia</PERSON> 1-1. Goalies: Skidmore, <PERSON>Nick Peterson,</PERSON> 8 saves; Utica, Anthony Caruso, 4 saves. <LOCATION>ALBANY</LOCATION> The Chargers scored three goals in a period of 11:18 to hand the Golden Knights their first loss of the season at Dr. <PERSON>R. Mark</PERSON> and <PERSON>Kathleen Sullivan</PERSON> Field at the <ORGANIZATION>Christian Plumeri Sports Complex. Joe D</ORGANIZATION> Antonio, <PERSON>Jean Carlos Rafael</PERSON> and <PERSON>Gui Dos Santos</PERSON> scored in the first half, and <PERSON>Andrew Nunez</PERSON> scored an insurance goal in the second half. <PERSON>Jonathan Creem</PERSON> and <PERSON>J.J. Comeau</PERSON> combined to stop just one Saint Rose shot. <PERSON>Patrik Ohlsson</PERSON> stopped five shots for the 0-2, 1-2-1 Golden Knights. New Haven 3 1 4 Saint Rose 0 0 0 New Haven scoring: <PERSON>Joe D Antonio 1-0, Jean Carlos Rafael 1-0, Gui Dos Santos</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Andrew Nunez</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Edwin Carvajal</PERSON> 0-1. Goalies: New Haven, <PERSON>Jonathan Creem</PERSON> 0 saves, <PERSON>J.J. Comeau</PERSON> 1 save; Saint Rose, <PERSON>Patrik Ohlsson</PERSON> 5 saves. ALBANY <PERSON>John Remington</PERSON> and <PERSON>Ebrima Bakaar</PERSON> scored a goal each to help <ORGANIZATION>Adirondack Community College</ORGANIZATION> edge the Panthers. <PERSON>Alex Scoglio</PERSON> scored the lone goal for the 4-2 Panthers. Adirondack CC improved to 3-2-1. Adirondack 0 2 2 Pharmacy 1 0 1 Adirondack scoring: <PERSON>John Remington</PERSON> 1-1, Ebrima Bakaar, 1-0. Pharmacy scoring: <PERSON>Alex Scoglio 1-0, Steve Chikwem</PERSON> 0-1. Goalies: Adirondack, 6 saves; Pharmacy, Adam Hoye-Simek, 4 saves. COBLESKILL <PERSON>Melissa Sluka</PERSON> scored off a deflection at 77:38 to lock up a non-conference win for the Lakers. <PERSON>Erika Faulkner</PERSON> and <PERSON>Andrea Lisk</PERSON> scored second-half goals for the Fighting Tigers, who fell to 3-2-1. Oswego improved to <ORGANIZATION>3-2. Oswego State</ORGANIZATION> 2 2 4 SUNY-Cobleskill 0 2 2 <ORGANIZATION>Oswego State</ORGANIZATION> scoring: <PERSON>Kelly Adams</PERSON> 2-0, <PERSON>Toby Klein</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Melissa Sluka</PERSON> 1-0. SUNY-Cobleskill scoring: <PERSON>Sherlyn Thomas 0-2. Goalies: Oswego State, Christina Freg</PERSON> osi, 3 saves, <PERSON>Kara Peck</PERSON> 1 save; SUNY-Cobleskill, Misty Golden, 28 saves. ALBANY <PERSON>Rebecca Marszalek</PERSON> scored early in the second half to lift the Gators over SUNY-IT in their home opener. <PERSON>Laura Tisinger</PERSON> also scored for <ORGANIZATION>2-2 Sage. Abbey Hanehan</ORGANIZATION> scored unassisted for 4-2 SUNY-IT. SUNY-IT 1 0 1 Sage 1 1 2 SUNY-IT scoring: Abbey Hanehan 1-0. Sage scoring: <PERSON>Laura Tisinger</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Rebecca Marszalek</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Rebecca Doble</PERSON> 0-1. Goalies: SUNY-IT, Aubrey Campbell, 4 saves; <PERSON>Margaret Werenczak</PERSON> 1 save; Sage, Brittany McDonald, 9 saves. BURLINGTON, Vt. The Saints, ranked 33rd in the nation, scored a goal in each half to blank the Catamounts. <PERSON>Cara Riley</PERSON> scored her second goal of the season on an assist from <PERSON>Gabby Racinea</PERSON> in the first half, and <PERSON>Tabitha Tice</PERSON> tallied her third goal of the year on a rebound of a <PERSON>Brittany Pfaff</PERSON> shot in the second half. <PERSON>Laura Ettinger</PERSON> picked up the shutout and made three saves for the 6-0 Saints. <PERSON>Alyssa Kelly</PERSON> stopped 10 shots for 1-5 Vermont. <LOCATION>Siena</LOCATION> 1 1 2 <LOCATION>Vermont</LOCATION> 0 0 0 <LOCATION>Siena</LOCATION> scoring: <PERSON>Cara Riley</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Tabitha Tice</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Gabby Racinea 0-1, Brittany Pfaff</PERSON> 0-1. Goalies: Siena, Laura Ettinger, 3 saves; Vermont, <PERSON>Alyssa Kelly,</PERSON> 10 saves. <PERSON>HAMILTON Forwards Jillian Kinter</PERSON> and <PERSON>Anna Baldwin</PERSON> each scored, and goalkeeper <PERSON>Ashley Walsh</PERSON> turned away 13 shots to lead the <ORGANIZATION>Raiders</ORGANIZATION> over the <LOCATION>Great Danes</LOCATION> at <ORGANIZATION>Van Doren Field. The Danes</ORGANIZATION> held a commanding 19-7 advantage in shots on goal, but <PERSON>Walsh</PERSON> was up to the challenge, making eight saves in the opening half. <PERSON>Dani Britt</PERSON> made four saves for the <ORGANIZATION>3-4 Danes. Colgate</ORGANIZATION> improved to 2-6. <LOCATION>Albany</LOCATION> 0 0 0 Colgate 1 1 2 <ORGANIZATION>Colgate</ORGANIZATION> scoring: <PERSON>Jillian Kinter</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Anna Baldwin</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Klara Jenkins</PERSON> 0-1, <PERSON>Danielle Wessler</PERSON> 0-1. Goalies: Albany, <PERSON>Dani Britt,</PERSON> 4 saves; Colgate, Ashley Walsh, 13 saves. <LOCATION>ALBANY</LOCATION> The Golden Knights, ranked No. 1 in the NSCAAHendricksCars.com <ORGANIZATION>NCAA</ORGANIZATION> Division II poll, ripped the Dolphins in a Northeast-10 Conference game at <ORGANIZATION>Sullivan Field. Freshman midfielder Sydney Bond</ORGANIZATION> scored a pair of goals, and junior midfielder <PERSON>Christina Cuffari</PERSON> added a goal and three assists for the 3-0, 5-0 Golden Knighs. The Dolphins dropped to 0-2-2, 1-2-2. Le Moyne 0 1 1 Saint Rose 3 5 8 Le <ORGANIZATION>Moyne scoring: Christie Morano 1-0, Rachel Farneti 0-1. Saint Rose scoring: Sydney Bond 2-0, Christina Cuffari 1-3, Gianna D Errico 1-0, Derith Fernandes 1-0, Alayna Shaw</ORGANIZATION> 1-0, <PERSON>Lindsay McQuade</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Carmelina Puopolo</PERSON> 0-1. Goalies: Le Moyne, <PERSON>Felicia</PERSON> Tynan, 11 saves; Saint Rose, <PERSON>Deanna</PERSON> Esposito, 3 saves. TROY Senior <PERSON>Nora Tomlinson-Weintraub</PERSON> scored in the 74th minute to send the 11th-ranked <ORGANIZATION>Panthers</ORGANIZATION> over the Engineers at <ORGANIZATION>East Campus Stadium. RPI</ORGANIZATION> falls to <LOCATION>2-2-1. Middlebury</LOCATION> is 1-1-1. Middlebury 0 1 1 RPI 0 0 0 <ORGANIZATION>Middlebury scoring: Nora Tomlinson-Weintraub 1-0, Drew Smith 0-1.</ORGANIZATION> Goalies: Middlebury, Jocelyn Remmert, 2 saves; Elizabeth Foody, four saves; RPI, <PERSON>Stephanie</PERSON> Vargas, 5 saves; <LOCATION>SCHENECTADY</LOCATION> Senior forward <ORGANIZATION>Kelsey Powers</ORGANIZATION> scored both goals, including the eventual game-winner 11:28 into the second half, to spark the Dutchwomen over <LOCATION>Utica</LOCATION> in a non-conference game at <ORGANIZATION>Frank Bailey</ORGANIZATION> Field. <PERSON>Sarah Rios</PERSON> made five saves for <ORGANIZATION>2-1 Union. Utica,</ORGANIZATION> which got a goal from <PERSON>Erin Murphy</PERSON> in the first half, dropped to 2-2. <LOCATION>Utica</LOCATION> 1 0 1 Union 1 1 2 <LOCATION>Utica</LOCATION> scoring: <ORGANIZATION>Erin Murphy 1-0. Union scoring: Kelsey Powers</ORGANIZATION> 2-0, <PERSON>Lauren Winchell</PERSON> 0-1, <PERSON>Caroline Moran</PERSON> 0-1. Goalies: Utica, Monica Storms, 14 saves; <PERSON>Sarah</PERSON> Rios, 5 saves. <LOCATION>ONEONTA</LOCATION>  <PERSON>Ainsley Stoll</PERSON> scored three times to power <ORGANIZATION>Oneonta State</ORGANIZATION> over the Engineers. <PERSON>Leslie Dauphinais</PERSON> made five saves for 4-1 <LOCATION>Oneonta</LOCATION> State. <PERSON>Jessica Corrigan</PERSON> and <PERSON>Julia Wright</PERSON> each scored for 2-3 RPI. RPI 1 1 2 <LOCATION>Oneonta</LOCATION> 1 2 3 RPI scoring: <PERSON>Jessica Corrigan</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Julia Wriht 1-0, Alissa Peterson</PERSON> 0-1. <LOCATION>Oneonta</LOCATION> scoring: <PERSON>Ainsley Stoll</PERSON> 3-0. Goalies: RPI, Briana Earle, 4 saves; Oneonta, Leslie Dauphinais, 5 saves. <PERSON>HAMILTON Laura Denenga</PERSON> scored a pair of goals, and <PERSON>Kendall Zaharris</PERSON> added three assists to propel the <ORGANIZATION>Raiders</ORGANIZATION> over the <ORGANIZATION>Saints. Colgate</ORGANIZATION> improved to 2-4. <LOCATION>Siena</LOCATION> fell to 1-5. <LOCATION>Siena</LOCATION> 0 0 0 <ORGANIZATION>Colgate 3 2 5 Colgate scoring: Laura Denenga</ORGANIZATION> 2-0, <PERSON>Lauren Dittman</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Halle Biggar</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Paige Hawley</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Kendall Zaharris 0-3, Adrianna Libutti</PERSON> 0-2, <PERSON>Anna Reddcliff</PERSON> 0-2. Goalies: Siena, Beth Meyers, 6 saves; <PERSON>Alison Baillargeon,</PERSON> 3 saves; Colgate, Kirsten Lalli, 2 saves.