AREA COLLEGES: ZELLWEGER LEADS DUTCHWOMEN TO VICTORY <LOCATION>SCHENECTADY</LOCATION>  <ORGANIZATION>&#151; Union</ORGANIZATION> s <PERSON>Isabel Zellweger</PERSON> scored twice to lead the field hockey team to a 4-1 non-league win over <LOCATION>SUNY-New Paltz</LOCATION> on <LOCATION>Wednesday. Union</LOCATION> (9-7) also got goals from <ORGANIZATION>Kelsey Powers</ORGANIZATION> and Tyler Willey, with <ORGANIZATION>Powers</ORGANIZATION> chipping in an assist, as well. Freshman goalkeeper <PERSON>Mary McCune</PERSON> made her first career start and made seven saves. <PERSON>Stacey Miller</PERSON> scored for 9-8 SUNY-New Paltz, assisted by <PERSON>Lauren Nicomini,</PERSON> and <PERSON>Elizabeth Dini</PERSON> made five saves. <ORGANIZATION>SUNY-New Paltz 0 1 1 Union 3 1 4 SUNY-New Paltz scoring: Stacey Miller 1-0, Lauren Nicomini 0-1. Union scoring: Isabel Zellweger 2-0, Kelsey Powers</ORGANIZATION> 1-1, <PERSON>Tyler Willey</PERSON> 1-0. Goalkeepers: SUNY-New Paltz, Elizabeth Dini, 5 saves. Union, <PERSON>Mary McCune,</PERSON> 7 saves. SARATOGA SPRINGS <PERSON>Christine Kemp</PERSON> scored four goals and assisted on another for No. 7 <ORGANIZATION>Skidmore (15-1). Skidmore</ORGANIZATION> trotted out three different goalkeepers, but only <PERSON>Allie Sosinsky</PERSON> was called on to stop a shot by the 4-12 Hawks. Hartwick 0 0 0 Skidmore 3 4 7 Skidmore scoring: <PERSON>Christine Kemp</PERSON> 4-1, <PERSON>Katie Potter 1-0, Brittany O Brien</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Lauren Tobias 1-0, Claire Superak</PERSON> 0-1, <PERSON>Hilary Cranston 0-1. Goalkeepers: Hartwick, Mackenzie</PERSON> Chapman, 10 saves; Megan Campbell, 3 saves. Skidmore, Liz Catinella, 0 saves; Margauz Hoagland, 0 saves; Allie Sosinsky, 1 save. TROY <PERSON>Rachel Preusser</PERSON> scored twice to lead <ORGANIZATION>Castleton State</ORGANIZATION> to the non-league win, tallying once in each half. <PERSON>Kierstan Ryan</PERSON> evened the score, 1-1, for the 4-12 Engineers in the 40th minute on a pass from <PERSON>Jessica Corrigan. Goalie Briana Earle</PERSON> made 13 saves in the loss. The 11-6 Spartans also got a goal and an assist from <ORGANIZATION>Stephanie Paproski. Castleton State</ORGANIZATION> 1 2 3 RPI 0 1 1 <ORGANIZATION>Castleton State</ORGANIZATION> scoring: <PERSON>Rachel Preusser</PERSON> 2-0, <PERSON>Stephanie Paproski 1-1, Courtney Nolan</PERSON> 0-1, Flore 0-1. RPI scoring: <PERSON>Kierstan Ryan 1-0, Jessica Corrigan</PERSON> 0-1. Goalkeepers: <PERSON>Castleton</PERSON> State, Siobhan Whittemore, 6 saves. RPI, Briana Earle, 13 saves. <LOCATION>ALBANY</LOCATION> The Saint Rose women, ranked No. 1 in Division II, finished the season undefeated at 15-0-0 in the Northeast-10 and 18-0-0 overall. In the first half, <PERSON>Brittany Godin</PERSON> and <PERSON>Aoife Herbert</PERSON> scored within 3:04 of each other for a 2-0 lead. <PERSON>Christina Cuffari</PERSON> and <PERSON>Kelly Guerin</PERSON> scored in the second half. <PERSON>Herbert</PERSON> and <PERSON>Guerin</PERSON> scored their first goals of the season, while <PERSON>Godin</PERSON> tallied her sixth and <PERSON>Cuffari</PERSON> her eighth. <PERSON>Deanna Esposito</PERSON> made two <DATE>first-half</DATE> saves for the <ORGANIZATION>shutout. Southern Connecticut State</ORGANIZATION> (6-6-3, 8-6-3) got eight saves from <PERSON>Olivia Heffernan</PERSON> and two from <PERSON>Katie DiDio.</PERSON>  <LOCATION>So. Connecticut</LOCATION> St. 0 0 0 Saint Rose 2 2 4 Saint Rose scoring: <PERSON>Christina Cuffari 1-0, Brittany Godin</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Kelly Guerin</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Aoife Herbert</PERSON> 1-0, <LOCATION>Sydney</LOCATION> Bond 0-2, <PERSON>Nicole D Errico</PERSON> 0-1, <PERSON>Carmelina Puopolo</PERSON> 0-1. Goalkeepers: <LOCATION>So. Connecticut</LOCATION> St., Olivia Heffernan, 8 saves; Katie DiDio, 2 saves. Saint Rose, <PERSON>Deanna</PERSON> Esposito, 2 saves. <LOCATION>UTICA Schalmont</LOCATION> grad <PERSON>Jessica Strang</PERSON> had two goals and an assist to lead <ORGANIZATION>Union</ORGANIZATION> to the win. <PERSON>Melissa Mansfield</PERSON> added a goal and an assist. <PERSON>Abby Stohler</PERSON> and <PERSON>Mia Simone</PERSON> split net duties for the shutout, both making one save for the 13-4-0 Dutchwomen. Union 2 2 4 <LOCATION>Utica</LOCATION> 0 0 0 Union scoring: <PERSON>Jessica Strang</PERSON> 2-1, <PERSON>Melissa Mansfield</PERSON> 1-1, <PERSON>Caroline Gorka</PERSON> 1-0, Pearl Jurist-Schoen. Goalkeepers: Union, Abby Stohler, 1 save; Mia Simone, 1 save. Utica, Jocelyn Rivera, 4 saves. ONEONTA <PERSON>Julie Kessler</PERSON> scored on an assist from <PERSON>Briana Crow</PERSON> (Scotia-Glenville) for the lone goal of the game. The 4-10-2 Engineers got two saves from <PERSON>Stephanie Vargas</PERSON> and one from <PERSON>Deanna Amoia. Alyssa Rondo</PERSON> made eight saves for 6-8-2 Hartwick. RPI 0 0 0 Hartwick 1 0 1 Hartwick scoring: <PERSON>Julie Kessler</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Briana Crow</PERSON> 0-1. Goalkeepers: RPI, Stephanie Vargas, 2 saves; <PERSON>Deanna</PERSON> Amoia, 1 save. Hartwick, Alyssa Rondo, 8 saves. ADAMS, Mass. <PERSON>Danielle Parenteau</PERSON> twice set up goals by <PERSON>Jess Tietgens</PERSON> to help MCLA improve to 10-2-4. Sage goalkeeper <PERSON>Brittany McDonald</PERSON> (Schalmont) made seven saves in the loss. Sage 0 <DATE>0 0 MCLA 1 2 3</DATE> MCLA scoring: <PERSON>Jess Tietgens 2-0, Lindsay Borbolla 1-0, Danielle Parenteau</PERSON> 0-2. Goalkeepers: Sage, Brittany McDonald, 7 saves. MCLA, Jen Wehner, 2 saves; <PERSON>Kate Tsapatsaris,</PERSON> 3 saves. TROY <PERSON>Alex Penny</PERSON> made five saves for RPI as the 8-4-4 Engineers played to a scoreless draw with SUNY-New Paltz. The 8-9-1 Hawks got three saves from <PERSON>Conor Power,</PERSON> one in the final couple minutes of the second overtime, to preserve the draw. SUNY-New Paltz 0 0 0 0 0 RPI 0 0 0 0 0 Goalkeepers: SUNY-New Paltz, Conor Power, 3 saves. RPI, <PERSON>Alex Penny,</PERSON> 5 saves. DURHAM, <PERSON>N.H. Steven Palumbo</PERSON> sent the ball to the top right corner of the net 1:19 into overtime to lift <LOCATION>New Hampshire</LOCATION> to the win. <LOCATION>New Hampshire</LOCATION> (2-2-2, 7-3-5) has allowed just eight goals all season. Goalie <PERSON>Colin O Donnell</PERSON> made five saves. UAlbany (1-4-1, 5-9-1) got three saves from <PERSON>Scott Kessler.</PERSON> UAlbany 0 0 0 0 <LOCATION>New Hampshire</LOCATION> 0 0 1 1 <LOCATION>New Hampshire</LOCATION> scoring: <PERSON>Steven Palumbo</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Charlie Roche</PERSON> 0-1. Goalkeepers: UAlbany, Scott Kessler, 3 saves. New Hampshire, Colin O Donnell, 5 saves.