AREA COLLEGES: <ORGANIZATION>CSR</ORGANIZATION> WOMEN BLANK PACE ALBANY &#151; The <ORGANIZATION>College of Saint Rose,</ORGANIZATION> ranked second in the country among <ORGANIZATION>NCAA Division II</ORGANIZATION> women s soccer teams, scored three times within a 14-minute span midway through the first half en route to a 7-0 Northeast-10 Conference shutout of Pace <DATE>Tuesday</DATE> at the <ORGANIZATION>Albany Academies. Christina Cuffari, Derith Fernandez, Brittany Godin, Carly Pengelly, Gianna D</ORGANIZATION> Errico, <PERSON>Kira Duran</PERSON> and <PERSON>Kristen Bidosky</PERSON> scored for the 13-0, 16-0 Golden Knights. <PERSON>Shannon Murphy</PERSON> made one save as the Knights posted their 12th shutout of the season. Pace 0 0 0 Saint Rose 4 3 7 Saint Rose scoring: <PERSON>Christina Cuffari 1-0, Derith Fernandez</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Brittany Godin</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Gianna D Errico</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Kira Duran 1-0, Kristen Bidosky</PERSON> 1-1, Amanda Deck 0-2, Coco Eber sole 0-1, <PERSON>Amanda Schweers</PERSON> 0-1, <PERSON>Nicola D Errico</PERSON> 0-1, <PERSON>Meagan McKinney</PERSON> 0-1. Goalkeepers: Pace, <PERSON>Courtenay</PERSON> Hagen, 10 saves; Saint Rose, Shannon Murphy, 3 saves. NORTH ADAMS, <LOCATION>Mass.</LOCATION>  <ORGANIZATION>Massachusetts College of Liberal Arts</ORGANIZATION> spotted the Engineers a goal in the first two minutes of play, but then scored the final three to win its sixth straight game. RPI 1 0 1 MCLA 1 2 3 RPI scoring: <PERSON>Nikki Goodsell</PERSON> 1-0, <ORGANIZATION>Kelsey Byrne 0-1. MCLA</ORGANIZATION> scoring: <PERSON>Jess Tiegens 1-1, Lindsay Borbolla 1-0, Gaby Fernandez 1-0, Jade Prickett</PERSON> 0-1, <PERSON>Brianna Bressett</PERSON> 0-1. Goalkeepers: RPI, Melissa Pinsonneault, 4 saves; MCLA, Jen Wehner, 16 saves. PLATTSBURGH <PERSON>John Mara</PERSON> scored at 51:25 to help Union (9-3-2) earn a tie with <ORGANIZATION>Plattsburgh (11-2-3). Union</ORGANIZATION> 0 1 0 0 1 <LOCATION>Plattsburgh</LOCATION> 1 0 0 0 1 Union scoring: <PERSON>John Mara</PERSON> 1-0. <LOCATION>Plattsburgh</LOCATION> scoring: <PERSON>Pat Shaughnessy</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Brandon Levine</PERSON> 0-1, <PERSON>Erik Hakim</PERSON> 0-1. Goalkeepers: Union, <PERSON>Mike Szczesniak,</PERSON> 0 saves; Plattsburgh, Andy Heighington, 3 saves. TROY RPI scored a pair of first-half goals to give head coach <PERSON>Bridget LaNoir</PERSON> her 71st career win. <LOCATION>Utica</LOCATION> 0 0 0 RPI 2 0 2 RPI scoring: <PERSON>Joanna Aliprando 1-0, Kerri Clark</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Megan McNamara</PERSON> 0-1. Goalkeepers: Utica, Monica Storms, 4 saves; RPI, Sarah Burcher, 8 saves.