AREA COLLEGES: BUREK, BOWLES LIFT UALBANY TO WIN OVER <PERSON>GEORGE MASON</PERSON> ALBANY &#151; <PERSON>Rachael Burek</PERSON> scored three goals and assisted on five others, and <PERSON>Rachel Bowles</PERSON> scored five goals as UAlbany beat <PERSON>George Mason,</PERSON> 17-5, <DATE>Wednesday</DATE> in a non-conference women s lacrosse game. <PERSON>Burek</PERSON> scored three times, and <PERSON>Bowles</PERSON> had two goals, as the 4-2 Great <PERSON>Danes</PERSON> scored the first nine goals of the game. <PERSON>George Mason</PERSON> 2 <DATE>3 5 UAlbany 12 5 17</DATE>  <ORGANIZATION>George Mason</ORGANIZATION> scoring: <PERSON>Allie Hilderbrandt</PERSON> 2-0, <PERSON>Caitlin Formato</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Rachel Obregon</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Kirstin Russell 1-0.</PERSON> UAlbany scoring: <PERSON>Rachel Bowles</PERSON> 5-0, <PERSON>Jess Antelmi</PERSON> 4-0, <PERSON>Rachael Burek</PERSON> 3-5, <PERSON>Nichole Eamer</PERSON> 2-1, <PERSON>Allie Phelan</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Christine Johnson</PERSON> 1-0. <PERSON>Maureen Keggins</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Amanda Obenshain</PERSON> 0-3, <PERSON>Julie Cryderman</PERSON> 0-1. Goaltenders: <PERSON>George Mason, Brittany</PERSON> Pastrana, 1 save; <PERSON>Caroline Brouse,</PERSON> 9 saves, UAlbany, Anna Berman, 7 saves; Courtney Henderson, 1 save. WEST PALM BEACH, Fla. <PERSON>Alissa Peterson</PERSON> and <PERSON>Erin Riley</PERSON> both had three goals, and 12 other players had goals, as the Engineers improved to 3-0. <DATE>RPI 13 7 20</DATE> Ohio Wesleyan 3 0 3 RPI scoring: <PERSON>Alissa Peterson</PERSON> 3-0, <PERSON>Erin Riley</PERSON> 3-0, <PERSON>Meg Colitz</PERSON> 2-1, <PERSON>Michelle Denny 2-0, Maeve Conway</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Shannon Maguire</PERSON> 1-1, <PERSON>Rachel Scofield</PERSON> 1-1, <PERSON>Sara Bischof</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Emily Essig</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Jamie Wakefield</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Lauren Miller</PERSON> 1-1, <PERSON>Lydia Wolter</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Audrey Stapleton</PERSON> 1-1, <PERSON>Erin Pomerantz</PERSON> 1-0. <LOCATION>Ohio Wesleyan</LOCATION> scoring: <PERSON>Meg Doherty</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Annie Swanson</PERSON> 1-0, <PERSON>Meredith Wholley</PERSON> 1-0. Goaltenders: RPI, Allie Arnal, 6 saves; <PERSON>Erin</PERSON> Amarello, 0 saves, <LOCATION>Ohio</LOCATION> Wesleyan, Daylin Stevens, 4 saves; <PERSON>Jordan</PERSON> Bernstein, 4 saves. <LOCATION>UTICA</LOCATION> Louise Steele-Norton scored five goals as the 4-0 Pioneers beat the 0-2 Gators. <PERSON>Alexa Pajak</PERSON> scored two of Sage s goals. Sage 1 2 3 <LOCATION>Utica</LOCATION>  <DATE>13 6 19</DATE> Sage scoring; <PERSON>Alexa Pajak 2-0, Mallory Hansen</PERSON> 1-0. <LOCATION>Utica</LOCATION> scoring: <PERSON>Louise Steele-Norton 5-2, Megan Kane</PERSON> 3-0, <PERSON>Patricia Kane</PERSON> 3-0, <PERSON>Colleen Dowling</PERSON> 2-2, <ORGANIZATION>Morgan DuPont</ORGANIZATION> 2-2, Julia Primps 1-1, <PERSON>Vanessa Maines</PERSON> 1-3, <PERSON>Courtney Wheeler</PERSON> 1-2, <PERSON>Lindsey Gelles</PERSON> 0-2. Goaltenders: Sage, Courtney Reed, 11 saves. Utica, <PERSON>Stephanie</PERSON> Belanger, 1 save. WEST CHESTER, <LOCATION>Pa.</LOCATION> The Golden Knights fell to 2-12 with a pair of losses against the defending <ORGANIZATION>NCAA</ORGANIZATION> Division II national champion Golden Rams. <PERSON>Zach Bellinger</PERSON> homered in the first game for Saint Rose, and both <ORGANIZATION>Derel Reed</ORGANIZATION> and <PERSON>Chad Adams</PERSON> drove in a pair of runs in the second game. Saint Rose 020 010 0 3 5 1 West Chester 220 000 x 4 6 1 Gould, <PERSON>Carr (3), Charron</PERSON> (6) and Capone; McCuch, Swearingen (4), Close (5), Roehrich (6), Weary (7) and Frazier. Saint Rose 021 000 2 5 9 0 West Chester 430 002 x 9 11 1 Venier, <PERSON>Buckley</PERSON> (1), Zareski (2), <PERSON>Johnson</PERSON> (2), Pokrentkowski (5), Perez (6) and Griffin; Kerins, <PERSON>Schwartz (3), Scull (5), McAllister (6), Hickson</PERSON> (7) and Roman, Frazier.